Office of the Provost and Senior Vice President Records UA002
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Committee files and annual reports, 1963 -- 2003; UA002.009; 0.55 Linear Feet
  - Educational Policy Committee [1 of 2], 1985 -- 2001; UA002.009.060.00019 (Box UA002 Shared 1)
  - Educational Policy Committee [2 of 2], 1984 -- 1992; UA002.009.060.00020 (Box UA002 Shared 1)
  - Long-range Planning Committee, 1969; UA002.009.060.00021 (Box UA002 Shared 1)
  - Memorandums, 1969 -- 1980; UA002.009.060.00022 (Box UA002 Shared 1)
  - Museum School Program, 1976 -- 1995; UA002.009.060.00023 (Box UA002 Shared 1)
- Bylaws, 1918 -- 1987; UA002.010; 0.5 Linear Feet
  This series contains by-laws of Tufts' schools, colleges, and the Board of Trustees. Also included are correspondence and meeting minutes regarding proposed revisions.
  This series maintains its original order.
  - By-laws, arts and sciences 1 of 2, 1918 -- 1987; UA002.010.048.00001 (Box 48)
  - By-laws, arts and sciences 2 of 2, 1918 -- 1987; UA002.010.048.00002 (Box 48)
  - By-laws, engineering college, 1955 -- 1969; UA002.010.048.00003 (Box 48)
  - By-laws, graduate school of arts and sciences, 1955 -- 1969; UA002.010.048.00004 (Box 48)
  - By-laws, college of special studies, 1959; UA002.010.048.00005 (Box 48)
  - By-laws, Crane Theological School, 1955 -- 1965; UA002.010.048.00006 (Box 48)
  - By-laws, Fletcher School, 1956; UA002.010.048.00007 (Box 48)
  - By-laws, liberal arts and Jackson, 1955 -- 1974; UA002.010.048.00008 (Box 48)
  - By-laws, trustees, 1924 -- 1970; UA002.010.048.00009 (Box 48)
- Sol Gittleman files, circa 1970 -- 2015; UA002.011; .5 Linear Feet
  University records are closed for 20 years from the date of their creation. Records older than 20 years that do not pertain to student education, staff and faculty employment, and Board of Trustees records are open for research.
  This series contains correspondence, speeches, reports, and other material related to Sol Gittleman's tenure as Provost and Senior Vice President from 1981 through 2002.
  Separated from accession MS2017.036: Sol Gittleman papers.
  Materials maintain the received order.
  - Correspondence, speeches, reports, circa 1970 -- 2015; UA002.011.080 (Box 80)
- 2016 -- 2018 accessions, circa 1965 -- 2010; UA002.012; .55 Linear Feet
  This series is arranged in order of accession.
  This series contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list. This series may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
  This series contains conference and meeting materials, proposals, hiring information, and faculty development materials, as well as personnel files for five former staff and faculty members of Tufts.
  - Center for the Enhancement of Learning and Teaching (CELT) and Tufts Teaching Conference files, circa 1985 -- 2005; UA002.012.081; 0.3 Linear Feet (Box 81)
    Transferred by the Office of the Provost, 2016, accession UA-2017-029.
    This file contains conference and meeting materials, proposals, hiring information, and faculty development materials.
  - Personnel files, circa 1965 -- 2010; UA002.012.082; .25 Linear Feet (Box 82)
    Transferred by the Office of the Provost, 2018, accession UA-2019-015.
    This file contains personnel folders for Lawrence Bacow, twelfth president of Tufts; Robert Guertin, former physics faculty at Tufts; Burton Hallowell, ninth president of Tufts; Steven Manos, former Executive Vice President of Tufts; and Robert Sternberg, former Dean of the College of Arts and Sciences at Tufts. Folders contain personnel data, correspondence, and policy information.
    Records containing information related to student education, staff and faculty employment, and Board of Trustees records are closed for 75 years from the date of creation. University records are closed for 20 years from the date of creation. Records older than 20 years that do not pertain to student education, staff and faculty employment and Board of Trustees records are open for research. This file may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
- David Harris files, UA002.013; 35 Digital Object(s) 35 digital objects comprising 13,423 files.; 18.3 Gigabytes
  - Office files, UA002.013.001
    - Email Announcement Archives, 2014 -- 2017; UA002.013.00001; 40 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes
      Accessions
      UA-2018-057
      This file contains email announcements and drafts from FY2015 through FY2017.
    - Annual Reports (from Schools), 2001--2016; UA002.013.00002; 1 Digital Object(s) Zip file contains 303 files.; 61.3 Megabytes
    - Bridging Differences Task Force, 2017--2018; UA002.013.00003; 1 Digital Object(s) Zip file containing 21 files.; .44 Megabytes
    - Centers and Institutes, 2006--2013; UA002.013.00004; 1 Digital Object(s) Zip file contains 16 files.; .51 Megabytes
    - CTSA, 2007--2013; UA002.013.00005; 1 Digital Object(s) Zip file containing 18 files.; 2.38 Megabytes
    - David Harris, 2012--2016; UA002.013.00006; 1 Digital Object(s) Zip file containing 23 files.; .2 Megabytes
    - Diversity, 2004--2013; UA002.013.00007; 1 Digital Object(s) Zip file containing 1181 files.; 1 Gigabytes
    - Email Announcement Archives, 2015--2017; UA002.013.00008; 1 Digital Object(s) Zip file containing 41 files.; 14 Megabytes
    - Endowed Professorships, 2013--2014; UA002.013.00009; 1 Digital Object(s) Zip file containing 3 files.; .43 Megabytes
    - Faculty Affairs Working Group (FAWG), 2010--2017; UA002.013.00010; 1 Digital Object(s) Zip file containing 124 files.; 9.1 Megabytes
    - Faculty Bylaws, 2001--2018; UA002.013.00011; 1 Digital Object(s) Zip file containing 36 files.; 5.7 Megabytes
    - Faculty Titles, 2013--2014; UA002.013.00012; 1 Digital Object(s) Zip file containing 4 files.; .12 Megabytes
    - Forms and Policies, 2006--2015; UA002.013.00013; 1 Digital Object(s) Zip file containing 87 files.; 7.43 Megabytes
    - HNRCA, 2008--2013; UA002.013.00014; 1 Digital Object(s) Zip file containing 32 files.; 8.6 Megabytes
    - Innovates and Collaborates, 2010--2018; UA002.013.00015; 1 Digital Object(s) Zip file containing 3532 files.; 1.1 Gigabytes
    - New Degree & Certificate Programs, 2007--2018; UA002.013.00016; 1 Digital Object(s) Zip file containing 569 files.; 398.8 Megabytes
    - New T&P faculty trustee event, 2014--2017; UA002.013.00017; 1 Digital Object(s) Zip file containing 116 files.; 194.3 Megabytes
    - One Time Events, 2009--2016; UA002.013.00018; 4 Digital Object(s) Two zip files containing 597 files.; 7.6 GB Megabytes
    - Online Learning (Mary Y Lee's files), 2010--2014; UA002.013.00019; 1 Digital Object(s) Zip file containing 83 files.; 115.1 Megabytes
    - Organizational Charts, 2007--2017; UA002.013.00020; 1 Digital Object(s) Zip file containing 139 files.; 24.2 Megabytes
    - Pictures, 2005--2016; UA002.013.00021; 1 Digital Object(s) Zip file containing 1543 files.; 3.9 Gigabytes
    - Provost Council Meetings, 2003--2018; UA002.013.00022; 1 Digital Object(s) Zip file containing 1094 files.; 25.3 Megabytes
    - Provost's Files to DCA, 2001--2018; UA002.013.00023; 1 Digital Object(s) Zip file containing 621 files.; 119 Megabytes
    - Provost's Office General, 2013--2017; UA002.013.00024; 1 Digital Object(s) Zip file containing 33 files.; 65 Megabytes
    - Provost's Retreat, 2005--2017; UA002.013.00025; 1 Digital Object(s) Zip file containing 188 files.; 80 Megabytes
    - School Handbooks and T&P Policies, 2009--2017; UA002.013.00026; 1 Digital Object(s) Zip file containing 35 files.; 6 Megabytes
    - T10 Strategic Planning, 2012--2015; UA002.013.00027; 1 Digital Object(s) Zip file containing 568 files.; 1.1 Gigabytes
    - TIE, 2010--2015; UA002.013.00028; 1 Digital Object(s) Zip file containing 215 files.; 1.2 Gigabytes
    - TII, 2012; UA002.013.00029; 1 Digital Object(s) Zip file containing 1 file.; 29 Kilobytes
    - Tufts Century Ride, 2012--2017; UA002.013.00030; 1 Digital Object(s) Zip file containing 618 files.; 1.9 Gigabytes
    - Tufts Global Health Council (TGHC), 2009--2015; UA002.013.00031; 1 Digital Object(s) Zip file containing 301 files.; 135 Megabytes
    - UCTFD, 2005--2016; UA002.013.00032; 1 Digital Object(s) Zip file containing 1217 files.; 136 Megabytes
    - University and Distinguished Professorships, 2010--2017; UA002.013.00033; 1 Digital Object(s) Zip file containing 17 files.; 3.1 Megabytes
    - University Professor events, 2014--2015; UA002.013.00034; 1 Digital Object(s) Zip file containing 9 files.; 2.5 Megabytes
    - Unfoldered Files, 2014--2015; UA002.013.00035; 1 Digital Object(s) Zip file containing 7 files.; 141 Megabytes
  - Email, UA002.013.002; 4.75 Gigabytes; 18,252 Digital Object(s) There are 18,252 emails.
    University records are closed for 20 years from the date of creation. Records older than 20 years that do not pertain to student education, staff and faculty employment and Board of Trustees records are open for research.
    Email will be made available to members of the originating office on a DCA laptop in the reading room only.
    - Email, UA002.013.083 (Laptop MCDCAL13182)
      Access to this material to the originating office is in the reading room only. Please contact DCA for furtheer details.
- Additional accessions, circa 1968 -- 2010; UA002.014
  - Correspondence, invitations, 1997; UA002-001 (Box 1)
    from "odds and ends" box, (unknown accession number, if any.); Added invitations from deleted UA095 (Office of the Dean of Liberal Arts and Jackson College) on 2012-12-10. See note in folder for full explanation.
  - OEA and annual reports, 1968 -- 2006; UA002-002 (Box 2)
  - OED, Title 9 and Boards of Overseers, 1972 -- 1999; UA002-003 (Box 3)
  - Subject files, 1981 -- 2003; UA002-004 (Box 4)
  - Subject files, 1985 -- 2003; UA002-005 (Box 5)
  - Subject files, 1970 -- 2002; UA002-006 (Box 6)
  - Vet school files, 1979 -- 2001; UA002-007 (Box 7)
  - Subject files, 1980 -- 1999; UA002-008 (Box 8)
  - Subject files and annual reports, 1981 -- 1999; UA002-009 (Box 9)
  - Personnel and A/S/E organization, 1981 -- 1999; UA002-010 (Box 10)
  - Subject files, Assessments - Fee, Tuition, Health and Activity, 1970 -- 2010; UA002-011 (Box 11)
  - Subject files, first year scholars program-Administration, 1970 -- 2010; UA002-012 (Box 12)
  - Subject files, 1970 -- 2010; UA002-013 (Box 13)
  - Subject files, 1970 -- 2010; UA002-014 (Box 14)
  - Subject files, 1970 -- 2010; UA002-015 (Box 15)
  - Annual reports, 2001 -- 2002; UA002-016
  - Medical Dean Search, 1991; UA002-031 (Box 16)
  - Medical Dean Search, 1991; UA002-032 (Box 17)
  - Emerati Card Catalogue, 1991; UA002-033 (Box 18)
  - T&P Records Catalogue, 1991; UA002-034 (Box 21)
  - Mary Y. Lee files, UA002-035; Lee, Mary Y.
  - T10 Strategic Plan files, 2012 -- 2013; UA002-048; Office of the Provost
  - Mary Y. Lee floppy disks, 2002 -- 2012; UA002-050; Lee, Mary Y. (Box Shared 8)
    Contains bags from 44 3.5 floppy disks
  - Institutional advancement design session, 1999 -- 2003; UA002-051
    Consists of design files, PowerPoints, images, word documents, and pamphlets created for Development and Alumni Relations for Tufts University. Original labeling on the CD was the following. "Tufts University january 15 2003 CGE and Y's Cambridge accelerated solutions environment." CD originally located in UA002.022.069.00023.
  - Penn State presentation, 2004; UA002-052
    Presentation given at Penn State College of Medicine, March 24, 2004, on "Meeting Today's Challenges in Medical Education with Technology." Originally on a CD in UA002.002.068.00016.
  - Understanding Managed Care: Learning the Essentials Through Presentations, UA002-053
    This is a CD-ROM that was transferred successfully by Dan Bullman, using BagIt in 2014-05.
  - College of Special Studies Re: School of the Museum of Fine Arts, 1983 -- 1995; UA002-054 (Box 19)
    One binder of photocopied memos related to the School of the Museum of Fine Arts, 1983-1995.
  - Dean searches, Arts & Sciences and Engineering, 2003 -- 2010; UA002-055 (Box 20)
- My Tufts Story video contest, 2020 -- 2021; UA002.002311; 2.12 Gigabytes; 22 Digital Object(s)
  Transferred by Harriet Chenkin, Assistant to the Provost and Senior Vice President, 2021, accession UA-2022-002.
  This series contains student films submitted to the My Tufts Story video contest organized by the Office of the Provost and Senior Vice President. The contest intended to highlight the many ways that students shape their learning and experience and was open to all currently enrolled Tufts students. The videos in this series won awards in one of the following categories: grand prize winner in the general category, grand prize winner for artistry and editing, first prize winner for each school, or honorable mention.
  - 2020 contest winners, UA002.002312; 1.04 Gigabytes; 15 Digital Object(s)
    - My Tufts Story, by Tara Aboumahboub, 2020; UA002.002313; 164 Megabytes; 2 Minutes
      School of Dental Medicine winner
    - My Tufts Story, by Jennifer Frye, 2020; UA002.002314; 27.3 Megabytes; 2 Minutes
      Undergraduate School of Arts & Sciences, Tisch College of Civic Life winner
    - My Tufts Story, by Krishan Guzzo and Megha Tandon, 2020; UA002.002315; 14.9 Megabytes; 2 Minutes
      Grand Prize Winner: COVID-19 Pandemic Category
    - My Tufts Story, by Amel Hassan, 2020; UA002.002316; 57.8 Megabytes; 2 Minutes
      Undergraduate School of Engineering winner
    - My Tufts Story, by Mahshid Iraniparast, 2020; UA002.002317; 55.0 Megabytes; 2 Minutes
      Graduate School of Engineering honorable mention
    - My Tufts Story, by Prayank Jain, 2020; UA002.002318; 94.0 Megabytes; 2 Minutes
      Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy winner
    - My Tufts Story, by Emai Lai, 2020; UA002.002319; 115 Megabytes; 2 Minutes
      Grand Prize Winner: General Category
    - My Tufts Story, by Connie Li, 2020; UA002.002320; 22.5 Megabytes; 2 Minutes
      Cummings School of Veterinary Medicine winner
    - My Tufts Story, by Sarah Oliver, 2020; UA002.002321; 2.90 Megabytes; 2 Minutes
      Undergraduate School of Arts & Sciences honorable mention
    - My Tufts Story, by Olukunle Owolabi, 2020; UA002.002322; 102 Megabytes; 2 Minutes
      Graduate School of Engineering winner
    - My Tufts Story, by Phuong Jean Pham, 2020; UA002.002323; 7.41 Megabytes; 2 Minutes
    - My Tufts Story, by Alyssa Rose, 2020; UA002.002324; 24.0 Megabytes; 2 Minutes
      Artistry & Editing Winner: COVID-19 Category
    - My Tufts Story, by Ali Sasani, 2020; UA002.002325; 282 Megabytes; 2 Minutes
      Artistry & Editing Winner: General Category
    - My Tufts Story, by Sukanya Upadhyaya, 2020; UA002.002326; 15.8 Megabytes; 2 Minutes
      Graduate School of Arts & Sciences winner
    - My Tufts Story, by Najah Walton, 2020; UA002.002327; 54.0 Megabytes; 2 Minutes
      Graduate School of Biomedical Sciences winner
  - Spring 2021 contest winners, UA002.002328; 1.08 Gigabytes; 7 Digital Object(s)
    - My Tufts Story, by Ariana Barreiro, 2021; UA002.002329; 21.2 Megabytes; 2 Minutes
    - My Tufts Story, by Tatyana Camejo, 2021; UA002.002330; 273 Megabytes; 2 Minutes
      Friedman School of Nutrition winner
    - My Tufts Story, by Nicole Cassarino, 2021; UA002.002331; 77.5 Megabytes; 2 Minutes
      School of Medicine winner
    - My Tufts Story, by Emelyn Chiang, 2021; UA002.002332; 147 Megabytes; 2 Minutes
    - My Tufts Story, by Elizabeth De Jesus, 2021; UA002.002336; 65.0 Megabytes; 2 Minutes
      Grand Prize Winner
    - My Tufts Story, by Katja Kwaku, 2021; UA002.002333; 281 Megabytes; 2 Minutes
    - My Tufts Story, by Lenor Levy, 2021; UA002.002334; 17.6 Megabytes; 2 Minutes
      Undergraduate School of Arts & Sciences, SMFA Dual Degree Program winner
    - My Tufts Story, by Sachin Vallamkonda, 2021; UA002.002335; 291 Megabytes; 2 Minutes
      Grand Prize Winner: Artistry & Editing